<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="no_help_available">
      There is no help available at this time.
    </string>

    <string name="help_page_intro">For information on the different parts of this app, touch one of the images below.</string>
    <string name="help_page_intro_html">
    <![CDATA[
      For information on the different parts of this app, touch one of the images below:
       ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section1">Topics</string>
    <string name="help_text_section1">
     Each help topic has a full page of information. 
     Long topics can be scrolled.
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section1">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        If you have an app that you want to add Help to, this demo app shows one way you can do that.
        All you need are two activities: one for the main Help screen and the other to display the Help 
        text of a selected topic.
        </p>
      <p>Each of the help topics has a full page of help text.
        The help text is defined in xml files in the resource folders of the application.
        If you use CDATA in the xml definitions, you can define paragraphs and text in bold and italics.
        Links are also supported.
       </p>
      <p>
        Long topics can be scrolled. Try this one in both portrait and landscape orientation.
        You will probably have to scroll the text in landscape.
       </p>
      <p>
        If you want all the details about how this app was constructed,
        touch this link to open a web browser:
        <a href="http://blahti.wordpress.com">blahti blog</a>.
        </p>
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
      ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section2">Html Text</string>
    <string name="help_text_section2">
     Learn how to display simple forms of Html in a text view.
     Paragraphs, bold, italics, and links are supported.
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section2">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        You can display simple forms of Html in a text view.
        You use the Html class and its fromHtml static method.
        See
        <a href="http://developer.android.com/reference/android/text/Html.html">Html on Android Developers</a>.
      </p>
      <p> 
        As shown here, paragraphs are supported,
        as are <b>bold text</b> and <i>italics</i>.
        The preceding paragraph has a link in it.
      </p>
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="help_title_section3">Links</string>
    <string name="help_text_section3">
      You can define links in the help text strings.
      To get them to work, you have to do some extra set up in the code.
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section3">
    <![CDATA[
      <p> 
      You can define links in the help text strings.
      To get them to work, you have to do some extra set up in the code.
      </p>
      <p> 
        To understand how to do this, study
        <a href="http://developer.android.com/reference/android/text/method/LinkMovementMethod.html">
          LinkMovementMethod</a> and how it is used with a TextView.
      </p>
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>


</resources>
